Did you
know that
the Great
Wall of
China is
not a
single
continuous
wall as
commonly
believed?
In fact,
it's a
series of
walls,
fort
ifications
and
trenches
built
over the
course of
centuries
by
different
Chinese
dynasties
to
protect
against
invasions
by nom
adic
tribes.
The most
famous
and well-
preserved
sections
were
built
during
the Ming
dynasty,
which
lasted
from the
14th to
the 17th
century.
The wall
is the
longest
wall in
the world
,
stretching
over 13,
000 miles.
It's
estimated
that over
a million
workers
died
during
its
construction
,
making it
one of
the
deadliest
construction
projects
in
history.
Today,
the Great
Wall of
China is
a UNESCO
World
Heritage
Site,
an
assemble
of
Chinese
civilization
and
military
prowess.